(Sheldon:)Perhaps.
(Sheldon:)But my mom made me spaghetti
with chopped-up hot dogs
(Sheldon:)whenever I wanted,
so who cares?
(Leonard:)Not once did my mother ever
give me any love or affection
for just being myself;
I always had to earn it.
(Mrs Cooper:)Oh, Leonard,
(Mrs Cooper:)I'm sure she loves you
very much.
(Mrs Cooper:)In her own cold godless way.
(Penny:)Yeah, and you certainly don't
have to earn my love.
(Sheldon:)Thank you.
(Mrs Cooper:)Of course,
you already knew that
(Penny:)when you bought me
this princess-cut drill bit.
(Leonard:)That's not what it is.
(Penny:)I know, I know.
(imitates drill buzzing)
(Mrs Cooper:)When your mom gets back,
I'm gonna need
(Mrs Cooper:)to apologize for the way
I spoke to her.
(Penny:)Well, come on now,
she did kind of start it.
Doesn't matter; a good Christian
would've turned the other cheek.
(Mrs Cooper:)On the other hand,
(Mrs Cooper:)a good Texan
would've shot her, so...
(Mrs Cooper:)I just kind of
split the difference.
(Mrs Cooper:)Hey, who's in the mood
for spaghetti and hot dogs?